http://www.freedomcircle.com/privacy

Home > Privacy Policy
FreedomCircle.com recognizes privacy is an important concern of visitors to its websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
Information Collection and Use
FreedomCircle.com does not currently collect any personal information about our visitors unless it is submitted to us voluntarily, as when using the Contact Us e-mail page. We may retain such messages in order to respond to your inquiries. We do not sell nor rent the names or e-mail addresses received in those communications.
We do collect anonymous or aggregate usage information, for example, to create the "What's Hot" summaries, which indicate what pages are visited frequently. If you click on an advertisement or product link, we receive reports from advertisers or third-parties which may show what pages, items or products were reviewed or purchased. However, the reports do not provide any personally identifiable information.
Information Sharing
Some pages of this website display third-party advertising. The companies serving such ads may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites to display ads about goods and services which may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit the Network Advertising Initiative.
Changes to the Policy
This policy may change from time to time. Any significant changes to the policy will be highlighted on our home page. This page was last modified on 19 June 2014.
Questions and Feedback
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by clicking here.
